<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book-Review on Tedsig42</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/book-review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book-Review on Tedsig42</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:22:36 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/book-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From Day 0 to 0day Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/book-reviews/from-day0-to-0day-chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:22:36 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/book-reviews/from-day0-to-0day-chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>MAPPING CODE TO ATTACK SURFACE Once we know where we are, then the world becomes as narrow as a map.&#xA;When we don’t know, the world feels unlimited. Liu Cixin, The Dark Forest&#xA;Introduction Attack surface (the potential entry points to exploit a vulnerability) often increases with the growing complexity of software.&#xA;The vulnerabilities to be introduced, as developers’ capacity to properly secure these feature is limited and mistakes are inevitable when dealing with millions of lines of code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Day 0 to 0day Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/book-reviews/from-day0-to-0day-chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:10:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/book-reviews/from-day0-to-0day-chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Taint Analysis Life is not like water. Things in life don’t necessarily flow over the shortest possible route Haruki Murakami - 1Q84&#xA;Taint analysis (or source and sink analysis ) is the analysis of the flow of input through a program from sources to sinks .&#xA;It relies on a simple idea: a large number of vulnerabilities occur because attacker controlled input (the source) flows to a dangerous function (the sink).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Day 0 to 0day Chapter 0</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/book-reviews/from-day0-to-0day-chapter-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:37:02 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/book-reviews/from-day0-to-0day-chapter-0/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone this is the first series of my notes and my recap of the awesome/incredible book From Day Zero to Zero Day written by Eugene &amp;ldquo;Spaceraccoon&amp;rdquo; Lim a security researcher and white-hat hacker.&#xA;He learned rapidly because his first training was in how to learn. - Frank Herbert, Dune.&#xA;With the number of discovered and exploited zero days constantly growing, vulnerability research, or the process of analyzing systems for new vulnerabilities, has assumed a critical role in cybersecurity.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
